easywebpromotion.com 2004-06-11

# BBFree.com - Free Forum Hosting Network

Hosting **9346** Forums  
Since August 5th / 03

|   | 

### Privacy Policy

* * *

At BBFREE we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our Privacy Policy demonstrates our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our clients. 

We use the information that we collect about our clients to fulfill product and service requests, and to create a more personalized online experience. When you register at BBFREE, we collect information, or Personally Identifiable Information, from you such as your name, email address and usernames / passwords. 

BBFREE does not sell or rent your information to others. BBFREE uses customer information only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting clients to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, and enhancing the user experience. At BBFREE you can be assured that your transactional information is secure, consistent with current industry standard encryption technology. 

The importance of security for all transactional information associated with our customers is of utmost concern to us. Our secure servers protect the information using state of the art firewall technology. All customer transactional account information is kept on a secure server. 

Please be aware that our site may contain advertisements and links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by the BBFREE Privacy Policy. BBFREE has no control over the use or disclosure of user data on other sites on the Internet and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of such sites to determine your privacy rights on such sites. 

Copyright Notice

All content included on this site, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, and software, is the property of BBFREE and is protected by international copyright laws. The compilation (meaning the collection, arrangement, and assembly) of all content on this site is the exclusive property of BBFREE and protected by international copyright laws. The content and software on this site may be used as a shopping, selling, and email resource. Any other use, including the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display, or performance, of the content on this site is strictly prohibited

BBFREE will remain committed to protecting your privacy online. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. When such a change is made, we will post the revised Privacy policy on our website so please bookmark this page and check back periodically. Any changes, corrections or updates to your transactional information can be edited during the ordering process. 

|    
---|---|---|---
